let quizData = [
    {
        question: "が",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ぎ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ぐ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "げ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ご",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "ざ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "じ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ず",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "ぜ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ぞ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "だ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ぢ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "づ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "で",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ど",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "ば",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "び",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ぶ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "べ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ぼ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "ぱ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ぴ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ぷ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "ぺ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ぽ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 5
    }
];